FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
EPISODE 7
- May I come in?
- I'm sorry, sir.
But this area is off-limits. No
unauthorized access.
I need to speak with the conductor who
performed last.
His name is…
Luca Domenico.
But the competition is still in progress.
Outside contact is not permitted.
Okay.
Choi Jeong-yo!
Jeong-yo.
It's definitely Jeong-yo.
There's no way I wouldn't recognize you.
Good morning, sir.
What's the reason for your call?
Go online right now
and watch the video of the conducting
competition in Brno right now.
Oh, right. The finals are today.
Why?
Did you see someone that you like on
there?
Choi Jeong-yo has suddenly returned.
Who did?
Choi Jeong-yo.
You know the one who went missing
nine years ago?
Don't you remember?
Hello, this is Pi-o Kang.
Do you know where Jeong-yo is--
I mean, where Luca Domenico is staying?
I'm here to meet Luca Domenico.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to leave.
We've been instructed not to allow any
contact with the press.
I'm not the press,
- just a friend.
- Oh.
Um, well…
It's quite late, and he's likely asleep.
Tell him Pi-o Kang is here.
He'll see me.
Please wait one moment.
Hello, Mr. Domenico?
I am so sorry to bother you, but
there is someone here who says he's your
friend
and that he would like to see you.
It's Pi-o Kang.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Domenico says he
doesn't know you.
He said he doesn't know me?
Mm, yes.
I'm sorry.
Is there anything else I can help
you with?
No, thank you.
This is the final round
of the competition.
Next up is Conductor Luca Domenico.
Jeong-yo. It's definitely Jeong-yo.
But why did he say he doesn't know me?
Today's winner, Luca Domenico.
Mr. Domenico,
congratulations on winning
the competition.
Recent accusations state you are actually
pianist Jeong-yo Choi,
who disappeared nine years ago.
What do you say to that?
I'm so sorry, but
I came here to make music.
I would appreciate it if you didn't ask
personal questions.
Are you admitting that you're Jeong-yo
Choi?
As I said,
I do not wish for my music to be
overshadowed by my past.
Please limit your questions to music.
Thank you.
Please answer! What were you
doing all this time?
As the winner has requested,
please refrain from asking personal
questions.
Further details will be provided later
to the press. Thank you.
Where were you for nine years?
Why now?
"I think he wants to avoid the question
because he really is the pianist."
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, is that Pi-o Kang?
- Hey.
- I-I don't know…
I'm sorry, but Mr. Domenico says
he doesn't know you.
He said he doesn't know me?
As I said, I do not wish for my music
to be overshadowed by my past.
Please limit your questions to music.
Thank you.
Prague police have warned that
pickpocketing incidents
targeting tourists have recently
increased,
urging both residents and visitors
to remain vigilant.
Authorities stated that additional patrol
units
will be deployed around major
tourist areas
and that crime prevention campaigns
will be strengthened.
In other news, Prague police are
expanding their investigation
into a recent rise in vehicle thefts,
particularly around residential areas in
the city.
Yesterday, at the conducting
competition held in Brno, Czech Republic,
Choi Jeong-yo, who went missing
nine years ago
during the Harmonie competition,
participated and caused quite a stir.
At the time, after police confirmed
a call demanding money had been made
to the organizers, they focused on
the possibility of
an organized kidnapping. However,
- the case was left unsolved, with neither
- Kang Pi-o.
- The suspect nor the victim located. "Our
- Where are you?
- Reporters did catch up to him in a local
- Have you
Uh…
- Brno hotel as South Korean
- seen the news by any chance?
I had to go somewhere.
- Netizens demand answers and insight into
- Um,
Why did you change your name
from Jeong-yo Choi to Luca Domenico?
- The man behind Luca Domenico."
- The one about Choi Jeong-yo reappearing.
The truth is…
I lost my memories from nine years ago,
"CHOI" CONDUCTS IN CZECH REPUBLIC
due to an accident.
Nine years ago,
at the Harmonie Competition.
Were you the one who…
abducted this man?
Yes, dead.
Are you saying you're suffering from
amnesia?
Yes.
Are you watching the news?
Kang Pi-o,
are you listening to me?
I'd like to present our budget execution
report for the second quarter.
Firstly, regarding performing
arts support, out of a total budget of
1. Q2 2026 PERFORMING ARTS SUPPORT PROGRAM
41.2 billion won…
"we've met all our execution goals and
BUDGET EXECUTION STATUS
succeeded in dispersing over--"
SHOCKING REVELATIONS,
FROM HIS DISAPPEARANCE TO AMNESIA
Ms. Kang.
Oh… My apologies.
So where were we?
Ah, I wanted to get your opinion on the
congratulatory speech for the Lucena
Grand Awards and the guests we should
- invite.
- Oh, right. That.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I suddenly got an important message
from work and I got a little distracted.
Since we've already paused, why don't we
take a quick break?
I have to respond to this right away.
My apologies.
Okay, let's all take a short break then.
SEARCH RESULTS: CHOI JEONG-YO
BRNO INTERNATIONAL CONDUCTING
COMPETITIO/ FINALS VIDEO
INTERVIEW WITH CHOI JEONG-YO, /
WINNER OF BRNO INTERNATIONAL
CONDUCTING COMPETITIO/
WHO WENT MISSING NINE YEARS AGO
INTERNATIONAL CONDUCTING /
COMPETITION BRNO 2026
Please, let me see him.
I'm sorry, Mr. Domenico has made it clear
he doesn't want any personal meetings
other than agencies and music magazines
and--
Oh, Pianist Kang!
Oh. How are you, Director?
I'm good.
I absolutely loved your performance
last year.
What brings you here today?
I'm here to meet Choi  Jeong-yo.
- I see…
- I won't take much of his time.
Just a brief meeting.
- Just a moment.
- Okay.
- Follow me.
- Thank you.
Hi. It's nice to meet you.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry. for showing up unannounced.
Was it a surprise?
Um…
You won't remember this but…
we attended Korea Arts High School
together.
I'm Kang Pi-o,
Feel free to speak your mind.
I can handle it.
Yeah, okay.
I thought that you were dead and…
to see that you're actually alive…
I'm just so grateful.
Why would you be grateful for that?
Well um.
Because you were my friend,
and I really wanted to make sure you were
okay.
So…
how did you end up losing your memories?
- Do I have to answer that?
- Oh, no.
You don't have to.
Hm.
So…
how did you end up conducting, instead of
playing piano?
Well, I mean,
your conducting was brilliant
and moving too.
But you really loved piano a lot,
so I was wondering if you quit playing
altogether.
You're going to play again, right?
What exactly are you trying to get out of
me?
Huh?
If that's the kind of thing you came
here to talk about, then go.
From now on, please don't allow any
personal visits.
I thought
I made myself clear.
Anyway, thank you for
coming back.
And if you ever
come back to Korea, give me a call.
Would it be okay if I gave you a hug?
Don't.
Mm.
- Hello, Mr. Kang.
- Have you arrived yet?
Yes, I arrived just now.
Alright  then,
have you thought about a way yet?
Hm.
Judging by  the  articles,  I think
jumping in  too  hastily  will only
backfire.
I think the best approach would be to
convince him that he'll be able to
make the music he wants to make.
And the members?
I think they'll at least be intrigued.
He's a proven talent returning after
nearly ten years, isn't he? That said,
we need to make sure that the process
looks
legitimate to
avoid accusations of collusion.
The concertmaster should be alright,
though we may have some issues
with the cello section.
You need to handle this with care.
I will.
But
did you really like it that much?
I know he was talented but…
Sir, you're still very much in your prime
so…
I don't understand why you're rushing
like this--
It's not a matter of whether I like him
or not.
There's a certain calling associated with
God-given talent.
Shouldn't we do what we can to help him
make use of that talent?
The president of Hankook Symphony,
Seon-ju Yoon, has arrived.
Ah, okay.
Good afternoon,
Mr. Domenico.
I am…
Seon-ju Yoon,
president of Hankook Symphony.
Do you still know how…
uh--
how to speak Korean?
- You're here.
- Yeah.
Um, Pi-o, is he here?
He's practicing today,
but I honestly haven't heard the
piano yet.
Are you feeling better now?
I bet it's a lot to take in.
But still,
it's a blessing isn't it?
After all  these  years of  thinking
he was  dead,
to find out he was alive.
So you got to see him.
How was that?
He didn't seem happy to see me.
- It was literally just a quick "hello."
- Hm.
Alright then.
I guess…
it must've been pretty uncomfortable
to have someone he doesn't even remember
acting familiar with him.
Did you tell him that for years now
you'd been looking for him?
- No, I didn't.
- Why didn't you?
You're the only one who never gave up,
even after everyone else forgot
about him.
You should've told him that.
In any case,
I guess everything worked out.
Now that we know Jeong-yo is safe,
once he settles back in
and returns to his music,
you're bound to see each other.
So, when are you…
going to practice again?
Jeong-yo's back now  too.
Maybe you should just
put your baggage behind you and--
- Are you here to lecture me?
- I'm just worried okay?
You've been gone for
a while now.
And that's for me to deal with.
You still…
need time to figure it out?
SINHADAM
Get going.
KOREA ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
I'm the king of the world!
Woo, woo, woo!
Choi Jeong-yo.
Be my practice buddy.
What do you mean?
Didn't you say you were busy prepping
for an upcoming competition?
No, I'm not going to enter any
competition.
I just want to practice with you and
figure out a way to let music bring me
joy.
You can help me with that, right?
Choi Jeong-yo?
Kang Pi-o.
You said your name was Kang Pi-o?
That's what you said in Brno, right?
Oh… Yeah.
When did you get back to Korea?
Not long ago.
I'm just here to take care of business.
- Why are you here at the school?
- Oh, uh,
I looked  online and saw that I went here.
Just thought I'd stop by.
I have no idea where to go, though.
Are you here just to look around?
Uh. Uh huh.
- So--
- Real  quick--
Why don't you go first?
No, why don't you go first?
- Okay, should I then?
- Yeah.
Um…
I'm really sorry about last time.
I was just on-edge and had my guard up
around strangers.
And I was exhausted from the competition.
I um…
I think I was pretty rude to you.
Sorry for everything.
No…
You don't have to feel bad about
anything.
Of course it would be weird for you.
Oh, uh…
If, if you're still a little lost then
I could show you around.
But seriously, what brings you to Korea?
Oh, I uh…
I was asked to guest conduct for the
Hankook Symphony Orchestra.
Really?
Yeah.
So are you…
are you going to do it?
Hmm,
I don't know.
I still haven't decided yet.
On one hand, it could be nice to
have a job in my home country.
On the other hand, it might just be more
confusing.
So uh…
Were we close?
We entered the Harmonie Competition
together, right?
You went out of your way to find me so…
I wondered if we might have been pretty
close.
I guess, yeah.
I would say that we were close.
This is the classroom where we studied
together.
You transferred here midway
through the first year.
You were a "gifted scholar."
Where was my desk?
Right there.
And where was yours, then?
Here.
Yes!
So do you recall anything?
I don't.
I guess I didn't take school that
seriously.
That's true, you didn't try that hard.
Then what did I take seriously?
This is where you and I used to practice
four-hands together.
The thing you were most serious about
was the piano.
Those practice rooms?
We basically lived in there.
What piece did we play?
Do you still know it?
My tendinitis
it flared up again
- so playing the piano is uncomfortable.
- You're in a slump.
- No…
- How did you end up in a slump?
That's not what it is.
You asked me before…
Why I ended up conducting instead of
performing.
Nine years ago,
I suffered a gunshot wound to the
right shoulder.
It was not the plan.
The plan
was to let him go after we got the money.
But
he put up a bit too much of a fight.
It must've damaged the nerves
in my fingers.
I can go about my life just fine, I just
can't play piano.
And that's why I switched to conducting.
But when I desperately want to play the
piano,
I play this.
While thanking Brahms for it.
I know how hard your predicament must be.
Take away music from a musician, and he's
left with hell.
As for your slump, well…
You could overcome it with a little
effort.
But I can't.
To be honest, I'd say I'm jealous of you.
Thank you for everything today.
Let's stay in touch.
Yeah. Get home safe.
And let me know if you ever need
anything.
Nine years  ago,
I suffered a gunshot wound to the
right shoulder.
It must've damaged the nerves in my
fingers. I can go about my life just
- fine, but I can't play the piano anymore.
- Was it for money?
Did you abduct him for that reason?
Or did  someone--
Enough. You want to know?
Three million lei.
Then I'll tell you.
Where have you been?
Then you shall again discern between the
righteous and the wicked,
between one who serves God and one
who does not serve Him.
For behold,
the day is coming, burning like an oven.
Says the Lord of hosts,
"That will leave them with
neither root
nor any branches."
You're home.
Are Pi-o and Father home?
Mr. Kang isn't home yet,
and Pi-o is in his room.
Would you like me to prepare dinner?
I'm not hungry.
Ugh.
Pi-o.
What are you doing here?
Where have you been, Mom?
I was at church.
Yeah, I had… I had lector duty.
So Mom…
What?
That article about Jeong-yo.
You've seen it too, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I have.
Gosh, I was so shocked.
Still, thank goodness that he's alive.
Are you planning to see him?
I already did meet with him.
Didn't know that.
So uh…
Did he…
- recognize you?
- No.
He didn't remember me.
Really?
Life is full of surprises but I never
thought something like that could happen.
Still, from what I saw of his conducting,
he still has all of his talent.
It's a silver lining, isn't it?
"Silver lining"?
Jeong-yo told me something…
about why he's now a conductor instead.
- Why?
- He suffered a…
a gunshot wound to the shoulder
nine years ago.
So no.
I don't know if I can really call that
a silver lining.
Oh…
I had no idea.
But you know, plenty of people switch
from piano to conducting.
Music is all connected.
It doesn't matter
as long as you can make your own music.
Oh…
I haven't done volunteer work like that
in a while.
Good night.
MARTIN VOGEL
CALLING…
Yo, Mr. Kang.
Hey. You doing well?
Oh, uh, if you're calling about Mr. Choi,
I don't have much to tell you.
I mean we both heard that he's already
dead.
No.
That's not the reason why I'm calling.
What is it, then?
I have another favor to ask.
What?
I need you…
to look into something and make sure
nothing leaks.
I want to know who the person behind…
Choi Jeong-yo's kidnapping is.
You haven't made your mind up yet?
No.
I see.
What is it that's making you hesitate?
Our orchestra…
You saw for yourself that when it comes
to skill, we come second to none.
You'll be given the authority to appoint
and dismiss orchestra members; it's
unprecedented control.
So isn't this the best opportunity
for your vision?
I guess it is.
Let's talk pay?
As far as I can tell,
what we're offering is relatively high, I
think.
Does our offer need to go higher?
No. It's not about the money.
Then what is it?
What's preventing your decision?
The truth is…
the reason I wanted to come here was
to meet Maestro Kang Seung-woon.
I have a favor I want to ask him.
What is it? You can tell me.
Oh.
You want to tell him directly
is that right?
All right, then.
I'll arrange a time for you to meet
together.
Okay.
Oh, you said you haven't chosen an agency
yet, right?
Well,
there's an agency I'd like to introduce
you to, if you're interested.
Could I give them your number?
What agency?
Jeong-yo.
It's me, Hong Jae-in.
So.
Do you remember me?
Now that you've seen my face?
I don't.
So you really have lost your memory.
Hm.
Still,
it's a huge relief that you're here.
You have no idea how shocked and
how sad I was for the longest time,
thinking you were dead.
- Sure.
- Hey.
We're friends, okay?
You don't have to be so cold towards me.
Here.
This is that picture I
told you about.
Look at that.
You can see how close we were. Just from
that photo.
Yep.
It seems we were.
Yeah.
You were a really special friend to us.
That's why Pi-o
couldn't give up on you
and kept on looking for you
for years after you were gone.
The only person who
never forgot about you and kept on
searching…
is your friend.
Why though?
Look at the photo.
You guys… were the closest of friends.
So uh…
uh, the truth is,
there's a reason why I wanted to see you
today.
BUSINESS PLAN AMENDMENT APPROVAL REQUEST
(APPOINTMENT OF PRINCIPAL CONDUCTOR)
NCAPF STEERING COMMITTEE MEMBER
KANG JI-HYE
"Luca Domenico"?
AMENDED PLAN,
APPOINTMENT OF PRINCIPAL GUEST CONDUCTOR
Heh.
Deputy Director.
What's this "Amendment Approval Request"?
Oh, that.
The Hankook Symphony wants to invite this
year's winner in Brno,
Choi Jeong-yo, to guest conduct for them.
Well,
this wasn't what we agreed to when we
approved the budget.
They can't just suddenly request an
amendment like this.
Uh…
well, this is
standard procedure whenever a
guest artist is brought in…
Also, Kang Seung-woon strongly
recommended him…
Welcome home.
Father.
Choi Jeong-yo…
Did you have him invited to the Hankook
Symphony?
- Yeah, what about it?
- Do you really not know?
You've never paid attention to Pi-o, yet
the moment that kid shows up, you…
Do you not care about your grandson's
feelings?
Why are you
playing the victim all over again?
How are  you still  so  immature  at your
age, huh?
Why does  it have to  be him of  all
people?  Can't you  see
Just how much Pi-o has suffered?
You still don't see the bigger picture.
Your son wasn't actually hurt back then.
Choi Jeong-yo is the reason he was even
half decent.
He was the only reason he won that
competition.
How can you even say that you work in the
arts
without having that kind of insight?
Pi-o won the competition entirely
on his own skill.
Jeong-yo was nothing but a roadblock
in Pi-o's life.
I won't let my son get hurt like that
again so Choi Jeong-yo…
Forget about bringing him in.
Stop being unreasonable and get out.
I don't have time to listen to you
throw fits.
Ms. Kang.
Yoon Seon-ju of the Hankook
Symphony Orchestra is here.
Oh. There you are.
You wanted to see me, Ms. Kang?
I'm sorry for making you come here
when you're so busy.
I just…
I have so much work, I can't really
leave my office.
Have a seat.
I was looking over some paperwork for my
review,
and I saw you were planning to bring in
another principal guest conductor.
Now why would you…
why would you want to do that?
Is that something that really needs
explaining?
You know who the conductor we're planning
to bring in is,
- don't you?
- Of course.
How could I not?
I was also grateful and elated to hear
that Jeong-yo was
alive and well.
Then, I guess I don't need to
tell you all about his star quality.
I think we should be commended for not
losing him to another country,
so we can strengthen Korea's music scene.
Considering his prestige…
his salary
would have to be higher.
But if you insist on having him,
I think we need to reconsider the subsidy
that we provide you.
Would you be okay with that?
Why don't you…
why don't you like Choi Jeong-yo?
What are you saying right now?
I never said I didn't like him.
Jeong-yo isn't
Pi-o's competitor any longer.
Is there
perhaps another reason--
Look here, Ms. Yoon.
Are you trying to make me out to be
someone who can't separate business and
personal matters?
All I want to say is that…
trying to chase after well-known
conductors like this
does absolutely nothing to help develop
our classical music scene.
Is that right?
I guess… I understand now.
What a shame.
At the end of the day, I'm a president
who can't turn down good business.
It breaks my heart,
but we're going to pass
on the subsidy.
And if we get Jeong-yo,
there will be so many endorsement offers.
I can't just let such an opportunity
get away.
Alright?
Try it. I heard
this place is popular so I stood in line.
Mm. It's really good.
Isn't it?
Am I right?
Mm. It's good.
Mm.
Here, try this one too.
So I complained to the manager of that
venue, "How could you handle things
this way?"
And you know what he said to me?
What's wrong? Kang Pi-o.
Are you even listening?
Uh… oh,
- of course.
- Uh huh.
I don't think you were listening at all.
Sorry. I'm just a little tired.
That's alright.
I wasn't… saying anything that important.
Honestly,
there is one thing that I did want to
talk to you about.
What is it?
Did you hear?
Jeong-yo is going to
join the Hankook Symphony Orchestra.
Did you know?
Oh…
So I guess he took the offer.
Huh? Did you know about that?
So apparently,
Mr. Kang had requested Jeong-yo.
He was the one who wanted him.
And it  sounds like
Jeong-yo also respects him
and wants to work with him, too.
That's great.
- He'll do well.
- I agree.
Isn't that just great?
Mm-hmm.
Then, how would you…
feel about being the soloist
for his very first show?
What do you think?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Well he's…
he's gonna…
do a concerto anyway…
And since he'll need a soloist,
I just figured
you could do it if you want to.
- I don't.
- Why not?
I just don't.
I don't want to think about performing.
Hey, don't be like that.
Just keep an open mind and
think about it.
If you remember,
you were always happiest when you
two were
sharing the stage together.
Don't you think it'll be easier
if you work to overcome your issues
together?
So why do I need to work with Jeong-yo
do that?
Do you think I'm so pathetic that I can't
overcome this slump on my own?
You know that's not what it is.
I just  need
a little more time to figure it out.
It's just going to take some time,
alright?
Oh. Mr. Kang!
Oh, Jae-in.
Were you out somewhere?
I just…
dropped by to briefly discuss something
with Pi-o.
Mm, okay.
That's great.
Come inside and let's have some tea.
Sorry?
So we meet again.
Hey, I had no idea that you were the
Maestro's grandson.
I heard you were joining the symphony.
That's great.
Let's go inside and talk.
Jeong-yo isn't even Pi-o's competitor
anymore.
Is there
perhaps another reason--
I need to find a way.
There has to be one.
It's not like it used to be.
There are so many ways to market things.
These days, there are so many young
classical music fans.
If we use social media effectively,
I think we can create buzz for the
festival without just relying on TV or
magazine ads.
Oh! Ms. Kang!
I had stopped by to discuss something
with Pi-o,
and Mr. Kang asked me to stay for a cup
of tea.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Jeong-yo.
Do I look familiar?
I'm Pi-o's mother.
No. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I heard what you went through.
Thankfully, you look like
you're doing well.
Don't just stand there. Either go
upstairs or sit down.
You're making my guests uncomfortable.
To think I'd get to see you again.
Truly, what a blessing.
You must have gone through so much.
So how did you lose all your memories?
Can I ask you that?
Uh, well…
I remember waking up in a monastery.
I refused medical treatment so…
a monk who used to be a doctor
treated me on his own.
And… When I woke up, well…
uh…
perhaps it was due to the shock of the
surgery, but I don't remember anything.
Oh, dear.
So that's what happened.
Yet you didn't lose sight and kept
studying music.
How impressive.
The piano. Are you still
finding it difficult?
Given his situation,
do you still want to push ahead?
Oh, Mr. Kang…
So nothing has been officially agreed to
between Pi-o and Jeong-yo yet so I'm
not sure if--
Then we can make it official here.
Kang Pi-o,
your friend says he wants to perform a
concerto with you for his debut.
What do you think of that?
I'm afraid this will be too much for him.
I'll recommend another soloist instead
and I'll let you think about it.
I don't know…
I really want to perform with Kang Pi-o.
He traveled all the way across the world
for his friend.
I could care less about his "slump."
I don't want to choose another soloist.
I'd like to perform the concerto
with Kang Pi-o, exactly as Ms. Hong
suggested.
Oh, Pi-o, it's actually just--
What do you think?
Are you not a fan?
I think it'll be a lot of fun.
Thank you for the offer…
but I don't really wanna do it.
I'm sorry, but
I'm going to excuse myself.
Pi-o.
Just a minute.
Just wait.
Hear me out before you go.
So… uh…
I just wanna say I'm sorry.
For talking to Jeong-yo about this first.
But,
I wanted to gauge Jeong-yo's interest
before I tried to convince you.
Why would you ask him about that first?
You should have come to me first.
Well,
that's because I needed to know what
he was thinking…
I'm sorry, Pi-o.
I shouldn't have done that.
- Let's stop this--
- Enough for today.
We'll talk later.
Later.
But…
Pi-o.
I'm really sorry
for making such a mess of things.
Ugh…
I should have seen this coming, shouldn't
I have?
I didn't think it was that serious.
It's okay.
I had a feeling he might react that way.
So…
Does that mean you
- still want to perform with him?
- Of course.
I have to.
Things are even more interesting now.
I'll call you later. Have a good one.
Thanks for everything.
Okay. Drive safe.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, hyung.
I just returned.
Where is it?
Oh, there?
Yeah, I recall.
Uh huh.
I'll be right there.
CHOI JEONG-YO
What was even more astonishing was your
unique interpretation of the set piece.
How were you able to accomplish
such a difficult challenge?
I couldn't interpret it.
Even if I go out there, I'll fail at this
rate.
I've already memorized it all.
Use it if you need it!
I just focused on doing the best,
and it led to a good result.
Come to think of it,
you went to the same school as that
competitor, right?
Were you close?
I think I need to enter if I want to
help Pi-o get back on his feet.
If he needs me to be his kindling,
I'd be more than happy to do that
for him.
No, we weren't that close.
- Yes?
- Hello, Mr. Domenico?
I am so sorry to bother you, but
there is someone here who says he's your
friend and that he would like to see you.
A friend?
- Who?
- It's Pi-o Kang.
Pi-o Kang?
I don't know who that is.
I'm truly grateful that you're alive.
Why would you be grateful for that?
Because you were my friend,
and I desperately hoped you were
still alive.
SPECIAL THANKS TO KO CHANG-SEOK
FOR HIS GUEST APPEARANCE
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
Are you still afraid of being on stage?
Or does the idea of performing with me
make you nervous?
By the way, how much do you actually
remember? And what have you forgotten?
Who was the gentleman playing the piano?
He was pretty good.
What do you think about doing the
concerto together?
Why do you go around telling people
you have amnesia?
You want me to break his fingers for ya?
Where's the fun in that?
Are you really considering performing a
concerto with him?
- Honestly, he doesn't have it.
- Then why don't you perform with me?